sup everyone David want to be five here
with a very special video now I don't
know why but I have been getting a like
eight a ton of requests for this
like as you may know I as you may not
want to sum up have videos I have eaten
the same Sonic Underground theme Mudge
I don't know the past eight years
or so and Allah p I've been asking me to
show exactly what it is so I thought hey
I know since since it's about lunchtime
why don't I just feel myself eating it
right now that way you can see what is
and how much I get to enjoy some of that
mmm ok first off I have not one
but two drinks I have a blue drink to
represent good old sock the fat ass head
touching the socks on the ground and
from the other drink I got Manic the
Hedgehog is brawl now for Bobby socks
lover I always have and make sure I
always make sure I can find the most
juicy thick yellow banana to represent
bottle be next I always get red
sprinkles for Knuckles a cool Echidna
then for Mindy I and you can move the
back I always get microwavable
burrito Luxa on make the brown yeah
that's good how's your microwavable
burrito or a Norwich plate for Mindy
Latour next to that I always get some
salami make sure it's pink
for Sonia the Hedgehog so as you can see
we got Knuckles Manic Mindy Sonia Sonic
and Bobby now I know you think wait
tables where's the chili dog awesome
sounds like you're fair food or some
well that's for hot dog too except
for chili dog Tuesday
there we go do that he prop it up a
little bit hmm Sonic hey so good let's
compare dramatic shall we it's up by the
way this is BlueBell this is this Manic
I could call it song barrier mana club I
don't know there we got the bow bottle
banana hey everyone how about try
Bobby's banana oh my God now what I'd
like to do is I like to take Bobby's
banana and just dunk it into Sonic's not
sweet fluid just dunk it right in there
mmm oh my God mmm oh that's good Oh
mmm oh my God I love that now I like to
add someone dug holes sprinkles into
Maddox sona just you justyou spice
things up a bit using it did stay over
there hey usually makes a test pretty
damn good so can see kind of turn right
bye I don't give a no more I'm just
enjoying this bit mmm come on
mm I'm a gun song on the warm sunny come
around get my bow the mall will be Pam
solid on the ground hmm oh yeah mmm you
like that don't you son got my banana
mmm crash a bob man you know what I'm am
oh my God mmm mmm oh my God don't know
oh yes no that looks so good hmm that
many days good browse come back
how do I get some brutal in this look at
that these are chunks of burrito in
there how do the does that happen
I'm done with that get up here no
I'm good still taste good mmm oh my God
oh oh my song and I'm talking so good I
just cry myself to Sleet
yeah I play them go oh that
oh my God a plus to ICU they know how to
make a good meal
thou shall go